What's up old man?
I see that you're a barking on another epic quest
You're gonna use your ochre unit to rescue the princess
But you'll need a magic weapon that'll never ever miss
It's dangerous to go alone, take this!
Ooh, thanks old man, that is really very nice
I can always count on you for helping friendly fights
Though I've never seen a sword of quite that shape of size
Oh god, that's not a sword, it's your dick in disguise
Yes, I can lie, I have painted my shoey
Now grab your destiny, if you know what I'll be
We don't need anything to be in the cave
When do you think you're outgoing?
This is a great chance to follow
Scrud and mad shot blowing
That was weird, but whatever there's no time to lose
I got a little print out as ever, and this chilled-ass groove
Wait, this isn't Gannon's lair, I'm a Liberty City
This place looks just like Philadelphia, but even more shit
I'm at the corner of Deadcat, the prostitute junction
Something in my acarina must've gone a mount function
I got a fix and quickly there is just a deal
Hold on a minute, Link!
Oh man, is that you?
This is a place I can't survive, it's just a sword in your wind
It's dangerous to go alone, take this!
Well, that's really kind of dirt, that's your wrinkled dick again
Look, I know I'm wearing tunic, but I'm not in demand
Don't be that great wish, let me introduce you
To my dream, that's friends, Mr. Johnson
I think you're a screw, if you see the pieces
You know you're gonna grab her, so why don't you try to come back
I am feeling about the gutter
Oh my God!
I got a war bat here, Princess Elder, wait, some must've beat again and door before it gets too late
Okay, now I really don't know where I am
Hold on a minute, Link!
God damn it, old man!
You're in Raccoon City, it's a zombie abyss
It's dangerous to go with a home chain
No!
Fuck you!
Fuck you, I'm not giving you, I'm not touching your wit
Stop and chill out crew!
Jeez!
Come in here, tell me you got a wee wee weapon
It's not cool, I'm not gonna touch it, I'm not gonna...
No!
So is that a no on the hand job or...
Okay.
Come on and click here to buy the album right now
It's got 13 great tracks that'll make you say, wow, like this one about Mario
Click here to check it out
And if the plumber's not used to how we got another one out
Click here to watch a video about Street Fighter
It's a music video, so go ahead and raise your lighter
Hey, riding raps, foreign and slates ruffs
So please choose your destiny, clicking one is enough